Guide to the Yale Dramatic Association Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Programs of Yale Dramat, 1899 - 1981; Series III
  - Playcraftsmen Programs
    - The Road to Venice, War is Kind, Nightingale, 1928 November 22-23 (Box 24A, Folder 60, Item 23)
- Music and Lyrics, Series IV
  - Music and Lyrics from 1066 and All That and We've Got a Lot in Common (Box 24A, Folder 61)
  - Unidentified Music and Lyrics Yale Annual (Box 24A, Folder 63)
  - Music and Lyrics
    - "Bermuda", "Yale Man's Lament", "Opening Number", "Let's Fall in Love", "Palter Song", "Love Song" (Box 24A, Folder 64)
  - Unidentified Music (Box 24A, Folder 65)
  - Unidentified Music, Lyrics and Scripts (Yale Annual Miscellaneous? Work Doesn't Pay ) (Box 24A, Folder 66)
  - Vaudeville Playbills Tivoli Theatre New Haven, September 17, 19 (Box 24A, Folder 67)
- Administrative Files, Series V
  - Yale Dramatic Association Presidents and Managers Photos, 1900-1902-1920 (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
  - Records of the Playcraftsmen, 1922 January 5-1925 February 11 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Minutes of the Yale Dramatic Association (Inc.), 1909 March 19-1929 January 21; 1935 November 19 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Minutes of the Yale Dramatic Association Executive Committee, 1911 February 15-1921 April 20 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of the Yale Dramatic Association, 1945-1969 (Box 25, Folder 8-19)
    General note
    1945 Mar 15-1949 Dec 15, 1952 Mar 12-1954 Feb 10, 1954 Mar 3-1957 Feb 20, 1957 Mar 6-1958 Feb 4, 1958 Feb 5-1958 Dec 11, 1958 Dec 12-1960 Feb 9, 1960 Feb 10-1961 Feb 1, 1961 Feb 8-1962 Jan 31, 1962 Feb 2-1964 Feb 17, 1964 Mar 2-1966 Feb 7, 1966 Feb 20-1968 Feb 6, 1968 Feb 26 1969 Feb 3
  - Minutes of the Yale Dramatic Association Executive Board, 1969 February 7-1971 September 20 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Minutes of the Executive and Advisory Boards of the Yale Dramatic Association, 1974 January 30-1975 February 11 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Minutes, 1975 February 13-1976 January 25 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Liquor permit, 1978 (Box 35)
- Financial Records, 1900 - 1968; Series VI
  - Yale Dramatic Association Manager's Book, 1904-1905 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Box Office Statements, 1900 May-1914 February (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Box Office/House Managers' Reports, 1936-1964 November (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Box Office Ledger, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Equipment Rentals, 1962-1965 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Subscription Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Admissions tax reports to Internal Revenue Service, 1945 October-1953 June (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Internal Revenue Service Correspondence, 1946 January-1962 October (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Financial Statements for Individual Productions, 1945 December-1963 March (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Financial Statements, 1900-1926 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Balance Sheets and Operating Statements, 1939 February 8-1947 February 3 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Financial Statements, 1945 July 1-1955 May 20 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Financial Report, 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 14-15)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Financial Report, 1957-1968 (Box 26, Folder 16-26)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Accounts Payable Ledger, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Bank Book, 1946 October 18-1952 April 18 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-General, Income, and Expense Ledgers, Circa 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-General Accounts, 1952-1955 March (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Cash Disbursements, 1955 April-1958 March (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Income Ledger, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Cash Receipts, 1955 May-November (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Cash Disbursements, 1958-1961 (Box 26, Folder 35-36)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Accounts Receivable/Accounts Receivable Paid, 1958 February-1962 February (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Income Ledgers, 1958-1961 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Cash Disbursements, 1961-1962 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Yale Dramatic Association-Accounts, 1968-1969? (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Tax exempt status - state and federal, 1955-1962 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Income and Expense Records, Tour Expenses, 1910-1935, undated, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Financial Journal for the period 1945 Jun-1947 Feb (Box 27)
- Miscellaneous Scripts - Scripts Submitted for Yale Dramatic Association Festival, Series VII
  - A Bad Play for an Old Lady (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - The Beggars Opera (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - American Blues (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - An Ancient and Honorable Profession (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - An Elegance of Rebels, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Animals (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - The Asylum (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - The Baby's Not for Frying (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - The Brothers Karamazov (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Casserole (Box 28, Folder 9A)
  - Change of Coats (Box 28, Folder 9B)
  - Circus (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Come Over Tonight, We'll Talk About It in the Morning (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Come to the Party, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - ( Come Out, Come Out Whoever You are, Bernard Mergendeiler !) (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Comings and Goings (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Corvino, 1945 November 25 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - The Days of the Commune, 1971 March 17 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Don Carlos (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - End of a Season, undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Enter the Queen (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Exodus 2000, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Everyman Replayed or The Trial of Everyman (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Fair Play, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Flight, (1940's early) (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - The Foundling - a radio play (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Frankie Baby (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Game of Adam (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - He Left Home (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Hey You, Light Man! (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - How Arthur Became King - a radio play, 1952 September-October (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - The Indian Wants the Bronx (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Intermezzo (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Jobson and the Grinning Skeletons (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Jungle Life (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - The Last Party, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - The Leader: Thoughts on the Instant of Greeting a Friend (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Lila, or the Death of Innocence (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - The Longest Night (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Martyrdom of Peter Ohey (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - The Men (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Morning (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Nigger in the Icebox (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Others (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Pity 'Tis, 1968 December (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Play, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - The Private Ear (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Professor Taranne (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Puss-in-Boots - a radio play (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Quotations from our Chairman Mark Rudd (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - A Raisin in the Sun (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - The Sign of the Four, undated (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - The Sparks Fly Upward, undated (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Spoon River Anthology (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - The Stick House, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - The Sting of Death or the Nigger of the Narcissus, 1963 Summer (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - The Theatre Whose Stage in the Street (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - To a Contemporary Bunkshooter, 1916 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Two Aprils Ago, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - T.V. (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Unidentified fragment (set in Russia) (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Untitled (on the Seven Deadly Sins), undated (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 28, Folder 61-62)
  - Viet Rock (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - Why You Shouldnt Go Rabbit Hunting on Your Honeymoon, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - Winter Son, 1953 December (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - The Zoo Story and the Sandbox (Box 28, Folder 66)
- Yale Dramatic Association Festival Records and Dramat Organizational Material, 1903-1975; Series VIII
  - History of Yale Dramatic Association Festival of Undergraduate Drama, 1957-1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - International Student Theatre Union Correspnndence, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - International Drama Festival, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 2A)
  - Yale University-Moscow University Theatre Exchange, 1956-1959 (Box 29, Folder 2B)
  - Yale Dramatic Association Festival Clippings and photos, 1967-1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Five Days (Yale presentation at festival), 1959 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Fold! Spindle! and Mutilate!, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Feifer Sketches (Paranoia Blues), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Theatre of the Soul (alternate selection for festival), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Consider My Wife (script rejected for festival), 1970 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Festival programs, 1963-1969, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 9-10)
  - Miscellaneous festival correspondence, 1958-1967 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Festival Correspondence, 1968, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
  - Festival Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Festival reports (Box 29, Folder 14A)
  - Yale Dramatic Association Records of Trials for Membership, 1903-1907 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Yale Dramat Articles of Incorporation, 1909 March 19 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Yale Dramatic Association Yearly Bulletins, 1910, 1911 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Yale Dramatic Association Annual Report, 1913-1914 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Yale University Theatre Fund, 1914, 1916, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - A Plea for a Yale Theatre and the Annual Report, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Yale Dramatic Association President's Reports to the Board of Directors, 1921 Mar, June (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Constitution of the Playcraftsmen, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - University/Dramat Agreement - first draft, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - 1930 Sinking Fund (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Proposal for a merger of the Dramat and Playcraftsmen, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - University/Dramatic Association Agreement, 1940 April 4 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Constitution and laws, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 26A)
  - Constitution of the Joint Committee of the Yale Dramatic Association and the Yale Glee Club, (1947) (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Yale Dramatic Association Executive Board "Manual of Procedure", compiled circa 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - "Undergraduate Drama at Yale" Report to Advisory Board of Yale Dramatic Association, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Dramat By-Laws, (1965?) (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Covell - Committee Report on the Future of the Yale Dramatic Association, (1967-1968 Jan?) (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Jones Committee Report on the Future of the Yale Dramatic Association, 1972 May (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Constitutional Amendment Proposal, 1972 October 3 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Dramat Constitutional Amendment "Convention", 1974 December-1975 February (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Constitution of the Yale Dramatic Association, 1975 February 6 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Dramat Advisory and Executive Boards, 1964-1975 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Membership Files, 1971, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 37-38)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1938 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence re: Dramat reorganization post World War II, 1945 June-July (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1944-1976, undated (Box 29, Folder 41-43)
  - Correspondence with Yale Dramatic Association Honorary Members, 1934-1961 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Yale Dramatic Association Correspondence with the American National Theatre Academy, 1955-1964 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence - John Galsworthy, n.y. March 10 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Monty Woolley Correspondence, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Arthur Sircom Correspondence, 1974 ? - 1974 September 17 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Yale Dramatic Association Autographed Menu - "The Good Natured Mangeville", 1903 April 28 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Radio Script on Dramat History for WOCD, 1945 August 9 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Dramat Historical Material, 1900-1976 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Material from Play Craftsmen and other dramatic associations and "History of Yale Dramat" by [illegible] S Naight, 1921-1925, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 51A)
  - Miscellaneous items, (1965 Fall) (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Old Stationery (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Illuminated Announcement, n.y. May 23 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - "Quote for the Day", 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Yale Dramatic Association - Monty Woolley clippings, 1925-1927 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Dramat Miscellaneous clippings, 1926-1975 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Drama School material, 1927-1975 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Residential College material, 1942-1975 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Drama major and curriculum, 1973-1975 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous, non-Drama School, non-Residential College material, (1919?-1975) (Box 29, Folder 61)
- Group Pictures, Series IX
  - With names, 1900-1951 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Cosmo Catalano, technical advisor, 1977-1979 (Box 35)
- Production Photos, Series X
  - El Doctore y el Infermo, 1907 October (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Merry Wives of Windsor, 1909 June (Box 31, Folder 2-4)
  - Merry Wives of Windsor - audience, 1909 June (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
  - Merry Wives of Windsor, 1909 June (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Audience on Old Campus, (1909-1922) (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Taming of the Shrew, 1910 June (Box 31, Folder 9-10)
  - Il Ventaglio, 1911 January (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Rehearsal of Devil's Disciple, 1911-1912 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - ( Robin of Sherwood ?), (1912) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Robin of Sherwood audience, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - (Harold), (1915) (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Troilus and Cressida, 1916 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - The Lodger, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - ( Twelfth Night ), (1921) (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Antony and Cleopatra, 1922 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Outward Bound, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 20-22)
  - Mural in Dramat greenroom, Circa 1935 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Production photos, unidentified (Box 32)
  - Photographic slides of productions (Box 33)
  - Duplicate programs and printed material (Box 33–34)
  - Children's Theatre, Catcher in the Rye, 1978 December (Box 35)
  - Folio
    - Pen and ink sketch, unidentified (Box 36)
    - Musical score, unidentified (Box 36)
    - Masque Dance (Box 36)
    - Hunt Song (Box 36)
    - Opening - Act I (Box 36)
    - Finian's Rainbow, Overture (Box 36)
- Photographs of performers and performances, 1908-1936; Accession 19ND-A-438
  - Importance of Being Ernest, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - London Assurance, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Lawrason Riggs, Don Porter?, and Harvey Warren dressed as female characters, circa 1910 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Racket, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Roof, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Wings Over Europe, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Yale Dramatic Association production records, circa 1978-1995; Accession 19ND-A-463
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle
    - Photographs, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Slides, circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chicago, slides, Spring 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Comedy of Errors, slides of credits, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Death Trap, slides, Fall 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Edmond, slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Guys and Dolls, slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gypsy, slides, Spring 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Kiss Me, Kate, slides, Spring 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lerner and Lowe slides, Spring 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
  - Medea, slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Three Penny Opera, slides, Fall 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ten Little Indians, slides, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified performances slides, 1992-1994, undated (Box 1, Folder 16-19)
  - Unidentified performances negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Commencement
    - Titles, final cut slides, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 21-22)
    - Titles, slides, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Titles, duplicate slides, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - The Wiz backgrounds slides, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Music and lyrics by Yale songwriters titles, slides, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Backstage and rehearsals, slides, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Cartoon sketches, unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Landscape views and Yale buildings, slides, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Titles and captions, unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Unidentified non-performance, slides, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Programs
    - Dramat performances, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 32-35)
- Production records, 1977-1980; Accession 1982-A-053
  Scope and Contents
  Theatre programs which came with this accession were integrated into Series III, box 24, folder 77.
  - The Good Woman of Setzuan, 1977 January-March (Box 1)
  - Sail Away, 1977 May (Box 1)
  - When You Coming Back, Red Ryder?, 1977 November (Box 1)
  - Ace of Clubs, Commencement 1978 (Box 1)
  - The Philanthropist, 1978 October (Box 1)
  - Cabaret, 1978 November (Box 1)
  - Makin' Light, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Trouble in Tahiti, 1980 February (Box 2)
  - Deja Revue, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Folio
    - Show posters (Folder 3)
- Records, 1937-1940; Accession 1983-A-083
  Donated by John N. Deming
  - Drama lecture: John N. Deming, notetaker, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Script: Too Many Boys, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Program: Too Many Boys, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A Stage Manager's Manual by Edward C. Cole, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Records, 1957-1979; Accession 1984-A-054
  Note: Pre-1976 materials incorporated into Series I. 1976-1979 items filed in Series II.
  - Script and production notes
    - Gypsy, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Design for Living, 1980 October (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Kiss Me Kate, 1980 November (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Tentative Plans by Michael Kaplan and John Levenstein, 1981 February-March (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Turning Blue by Amy Appleby and Charles Geyer, 1981 May (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - Chicago, 1981 November (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - Guys and Dolls, 1982 November (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - The Maids, 1982 February (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - The Caucasian Chalk Circle, 1982 April (Box 1, Folder 13-17)
    - Ten Little Indians, 1984 February (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - The Year In Revue, 1984 May (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence
    - Drama School, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Re: Scheduling of Theater, 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Re: Commencement revues, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Publicity and budget: The Glass Menagerie and Heartbreak House, 1980 Oct, 1981 February (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Preliminary budgets, 1880-1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Budgets and schedules, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Minutes, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Proposals for Ex theater, 1982 Fall (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Programs, articles, and publicity, 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
  - Photographs, 1912-1914 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Slides [show?], undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Audio tape Turning Blue, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Records, circa 1970-1984; Accession 1984-A-055
  - Programs
    - "Tintypes", 1982 Commencement (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "Fiddler on the Roof", November 1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "Ten Little Indians", April 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "The Year in Revue", 1984 Commencement (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Scripts
    - "In the Image of the Kings," by Tina Landau, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - "T Plans" (?), undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - "The Year in Revue", 1984 Commencement (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stage Manager's Book
  - "The Year in Revue", 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lighting plans, set plans, and posters -1970s and 1980s (Box 2)
- Playbills and photographs, 1920-1987; Accession 1988-A-102
  - Playbills
    - Programs
      - 1920 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1930s-1940s (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
      - 1950s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 5-7)
      - 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Photographs of Unidentified Productions, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photographic slides
    - Country Wife, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - He Who Gets Slapped, 1979 April (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Cole Porter I, 1976 May (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    - Unidentified play, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified play, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Various plays, mostly unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Exterior pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Interior pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Transparencies "specials": Yale Buildings, Washington, D.C., undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - WAR Pictures, Racial, Pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Financial reports, 1955-1971; Accession 1991-A-101
  - Financial Reports
    - 1955-1971 1955-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
- Posters and programs, 1990-1991; Accession 1991-A-110
  - Into the Woods poster (Folder 1)
  - Pennies from Heaven poster (Folder 1)
  - The Room poster (Folder 1)
  - The First Annual Costume Ball poster (Folder 1)
  - Program for The Room (Folder 1)
  - Posters and playbills (Box 37)
- Financial reports, photographs, posters, and programs for shows, 1972-1991; Accession 1991-A-132
  Conditions Governing Access
  Financial reports in folders 1-5 are restricted 35 years from date of creation as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
  - Financial Reports
    - 1972-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Contact Print and Negatives Commencement Show, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Photos Marie and Bruce, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1989, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Phonograph recordings, photographs, programs, and posters, 1900-1993; Accession 1993-A-084
  - Phonograph Recordings
    - Stover at Yale (2 copies) [Transferred to Historical Sound Recordings], 1954
  - Photographs
    - Stink Dover at Yale, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Programs
    - Cold Sweat, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Medea, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Noises Off, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Suicide in B-Flat, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Top Girls, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Posters
    - A Family of Four, undated
      - "Zandra's Daughter" (Box 1A, Folder 2)
      - "Danny and Faye" (Box 1A, Folder 2)
      - "How Alex Looks When She's Hurt" (Box 1A, Folder 2)
      - "Little Wimmin" (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - A Room Without Windows, undated (Folder 4)
    - Ace of Clubs (auditions), 1978 (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Ace of Clubs, 1978 (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - America Hurrah and The Only Jealousy of Emer, undated (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Angel City, undated (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Antigone (auditions), undated (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - The Antimacassar Massacre
      See: "The Rape of Blanche Dubois" box 3, folder 8
    - Anyone Can Whistle, undated (Folder 4)
    - Anything Goes, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Anything Goes (auditions), undated (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Anything Goes (director: Fran Soeder), undated (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Anything Goes (director: Hamar Kubovy, Ira Sachs), undated (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - The Assassin, undated (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Beowulf, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Bells Are Ringing, undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Blue Skies, 1991 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Breaking Point, undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Cabaret (auditions), undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Cabaret (director: David McKenna), undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Cabaret, 1991 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Can-Can, 1989 (Box 1A, Folder 3)